{
    "subject": "resource/Quantum_Hoops",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The film Quantum Hoops is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9837724566459656,
            "question": "Is Quantum Hoops considered a type of movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9243953824043274,
            "question": "What genre is the film Quantum Hoops?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7664343118667603,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other films in the same category as Quantum Hoops?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6658524870872498,
            "question": "What is the plot of Quantum Hoops?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6439309120178223,
            "question": "Where could one watch the film Quantum Hoops?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5667096972465515,
            "question": "Is there a sequel to Quantum Hoops?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40191811323165894,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors or directors associated with Quantum Hoops?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2500474750995636,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in films of this type?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22994723916053772,
            "question": "Has Quantum Hoops received any critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21087393164634705,
            "question": "What year was Quantum Hoops released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film Quantum Hoops is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6068_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Quantum Hoops received any critical acclaim?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6068_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in films of this type?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6068_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors or directors associated with Quantum Hoops?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6068_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6068_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents describe Quantum Hoops as a documentary and provide details about its plot, cast (narrator David Duchovny), director Rick Greenwald, and other attributes that are characteristic of films. Therefore, the statement \"The film Quantum Hoops is a type of Film\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that \"Quantum Hoops\" is a documentary film, thus supporting the statement that it is a type of film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}